### Contact

### **Phone**

0752 825 842

#### **Email**

crauciuc.costin@yahoo.com



### **Address**

lasi, Romania

# **Competencies**

- React
- NextJs, Vite
- HTML & CSS
- Javascript
- MongoDb

## **Projects**

- @ Car auction website
- Animals adoption

# Crauciuc Costin

## Junior Front-end Developer

Junior web developer at the beginning of the journey, oriented towards solving problems in the most efficient way, using efficient technologies to deliver quality software products.

I worked with languages such as HTML, SCSS, Javascript and React with NextJs or Vite, to create various projects from presentation websites to fullstack web applications for car auctions or animal adoptions. Out of my desire to understand the overall picture of web development, I also build an ecommerce store where I used more technologies such as Node.js and Express. All these projects matured me a little and helped me acquire valuable knowledge to create even more powerful and complex web applications.

My goal is that one day I will have the necessary experience and knowledge to build a large and complex application from start to finish. But, until then, I want to accumulate as much quality information as possible, to grow professionally and to bring value to the environment and the project I am part of.

## **Education**

O 2013 - 2017

**High School Diploma: Mathematics Informatics** 

Colegiul "Costache Negruzii" Iasi - Iasi, Romania

2017 - 2020

**College Degree: Accounting And Management Information Systems** 

Facultatea De Economie Si Administrarea Afacerilor - Iasi, Romania

2020 - Current

**Self-education: Web Development** 

Online Courses

## **Work History**

O 2021 - 2022

### **Junior Accountant**

Accounting company, Iasi

- Assisted with preparation of monthly financial statements.
- Utilized tax software to prepare and file tax returns.
- Registered financial accounting documents

O 2022 - Current

### Front-End Web Developer

Freelancer, lasi

- Designed and updated layouts to meet usability and performance.
- Researched emerging web technologies and trends.
- Coded using React to develop features for presentation websites of fullstack applications, both optimized for mobile and desktop.